OLUSOLA G. OMOLEYE

No. 6 Eagle's Close, Ijegun, Lagos.

olusolagabriel4@gmail.com +2347030529392

PROFILE

Experienced Pharmacist with successful background maintaining medication controls and patient confidentiality, Passionate and able to multi-task dedicated to supporting team objectives to facilitate top-quality care. Well-versed in monitoring and noting vital signs. Proficient in delivering quality health care services and provide satisfactory services to clients as well as working towards the development of the organization at all levels.

SKILLS

- Patient Care and Medication dispensing
- Counselling, Drug Inventory Management
- Patient Care plan, Patient Relationship Building
- Health Care Administration, Monitoring therapeutic effectiveness
- Effective work breakdown structure, multitasking, developed critical thinking and decision-making skills

WORK HISTORY

NOV 2020 - TILL DATE

AJEROMI GENERAL HOSPITAL, AJEGUNLE - LAGOS **Pharmacist**

- Provided consultations, counseling, and answered inquiries from patients, healthcare professionals, and physicians regarding drugs, potential side effects, and specified use
- Interpreted prescription orders, dispensed medications, and counseled patients on drugs.
- Reviewed patient medication profiles and medical records to screen for appropriate drug selection, dosing, contraindications, side effects, and therapeutic outcomes.
- Collaborated with colleagues, technicians, and leading pharmacists in effective prioritization and filling of orders.
- Evaluated appropriateness of drug therapy based on patientspecific factors and drug information.

FEB 2021-AUGUST 2021 AERIAL CARE PHARMACY - IJESHATEDO LAGOS

Locum Pharmacist

- Providing retails and pharmacy customer services.
- Dispensing medications and counselling patients on how to properly use their medications.
- Answering drug information questions from patients.
- Assessing patient's condition and making decisions about which medication that will effectively treat

OCT. 2019- NOV. 2021 AERIAL CARE PHARMACY - OKOTA, LAGOS

Full time Pharmacist

- Providing retails and pharmacy customer services.
- Dispensing medications and counselling patients on how to properly use their medications.
- Answering drug information questions from patients.
- Assessing patient's condition and making decisions about which medication that will effectively treat
- Advised patients on medication side effects and contraindications and explained proper administration.

2019 – 2020 PRIMARY HEALTH CARE, IJEGUN, LAGOS STATE Corper Pharmacist

- Stock-taking; drug dispense; counseling of patients on the proper use of medications under the supervision of the pharmacist
- Assisted pharmacist in the final review of filled prescriptions.

2018– 2019 OAUTH COMPLEX - ILE-IFE

Intern Pharmacist

- Drug Dispense, Educated patients on possible drug interactions, potential side effects, and optimal methods of administration.
- Compared prescription details against safety standards and insurance requirements to support patients.
- Evaluated patient histories to assess medication compliance and spot issues such as doctor shopping or excessive usage.
- Monitored inventory levels and notified pharmacist of items requiring to reorder.
- Assisted pharmacist in the final review of filled prescriptions.

2017 – 2018 SEMPER PHARMACY - LAGOS

Locum Pharmacy

- Inspected drug storage sites, monitored drug supply expiration dates, and verified proper supply levels.
- Verified and labeled prescriptions and Managed pharmaceutical supply procurement and management processes.
- Provided consultations, counseling, and answered inquiries from patients, healthcare professionals, and physicians regarding drugs, potential side effects, and specified use.
- Advised patients on medication side effects and contraindications and explained proper administration.

2014 – 2015 GRATITUDE MISSION HOSPITAL - LAGOS

Student Pharmacist

 Stock-taking; drug dispense; counseling of patients on the proper use of medications under the supervision of the pharmacist

,

EDUCATION

2010 – 2017 OBAFEMI AWOLOWO UNIVERSITY, ILE IFE

B.Pharm (Pharmacy)

2000 – 2006 OROONA HIGH SCHOOL, OGUN STATE

WASSCE

CERTIFICATES

| Infection, Prevention, and Control, Florence Academy | 2022 |
|---|------|
| CPD Certificate, First AID, Florence Academy | 2022 |
| CPD Certificate, Catheter Care, Florence Academy | 2022 |
| Safeguarding Adult (support and protection), Florence Academy | 2022 |
| CPD Certificate, End of Life care, Florence Academy | 2022 |
| Basic Life Support Training (American Heart Association) | 2021 |

INTEREST

At my leisure, I love to engage in research, writing, travel and engage in activities that help the mind to develop great problem-solving skills.

REFERENCES

References at available on request.